http://www.eeoc.gov/privacy-policy-us-equal-employment-opportunity-commission-web-site

Skip to main content
The .gov means it’s official.
Federal government websites often end in .gov or .mil. Before sharing sensitive information, make sure you’re on a federal government site.
The site is secure.
The https:// ensures that you are connecting to the official website and that any information you provide is encrypted and transmitted securely.
Breadcrumb
Home
Privacy Policy for the U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Web Site
Privacy Policy for the U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Web Site
We collect no personal information about you when you visit this site unless you choose to provide this information to us. Our web server software, and our content management system, do collect certain information automatically, and some of this information is made available to us. This information is outlined below. Information collected and stored automatically: If you visit our site to read or download information, the following information is collected automatically by the web server. None of this information is used to identify you. The name of Internet domain and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you are connected to a network, such as the Internet). This information is used to help count the number of unique visits made to the site; The date and time that you access our site; The pages you visit (which helps us to determine what people are looking for); The web browser you use (which helps us to design our site to accommodate the broadest possible range of web browser software); and If you followed a link to get to us, the page you linked from (which helps us to determine how people are finding us, and how we can reach more people). All of this information is used to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you. We do not track or record information about individuals. If you send us personal information: If you choose to provide us with personal information, as in e-mail with a comment or question, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it to us through our web site, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. Electronic mail is not secure. Therefore, we suggest that you not send personal information to us via e-mail, especially social security numbers. We may share information you give us with contractors acting on our behalf or with another government agency if your inquiry relates to that agency. EEOC does not collect or use information for commercial marketing. We do not share our e-mail with any other organizations, unless we receive a request from an organization conducting a civil or criminal law enforcement investigation. Electronically submitted information is maintained and destroyed according to the requirements of the Federal Records Act and the regulations and records retention schedules of the National Archives and Records Administration, and in some cases may be covered by the Privacy Act and the Freedom of Information Act. A discussion of your rights under these laws can be found at www.USA.gov. Social Media: Please see our comments policy and privacy notice for Facebook, Twitter, YouTube and other social media. Links to other sites: We may have links to other outside web sites (both federal and non-federal) that we do not control. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policies of these sites, and users should check those policies on such sites. Use of cookies: "Cookies" are small bits of text that are either used for the duration of the session ("session cookies"), or saved on a user's hard drive in order to identify that user, or information about that user, the next time the user logs on to a web site ("persistent cookies"). EEOC's websites do not use persistent cookies. Session specific cookies may be used to improve the user experience and for basic web metrics. These cookies expire in a very short time frame or when a browser window closes and are permitted by current federal guidelines. Security: We maintain a variety of physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the security of this web site and any personal information you provide to us. For example, this Government computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Anyone using this system expressly consents to such monitoring and is advised that if such monitoring reveals evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, such evidence may be provided to appropriate law enforcement officials. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information on this server are strictly prohibited and may be punishable by law, including the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986, and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act of 1996. Changes to this policy: We will revise or update this policy if our practices change. You should refer back to this page often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes. If we decide to change this policy, we will post a new policy on our site and change the date at the bottom. Changes to the policy shall not apply retroactively.
